Me? Hi.
I'm trying to relax.
Would you mind? Oh, sorry. Mr.
Hey, kid,
just come over here and sit down, would you?
What's your name? Mr. My name is Adam.
You look like my grandpa, except he's not as old.
That's very rude. I'm Adam. Who are
you?
Joseph. Where's your mother?
She's with her boyfriend. Supposed to wait over
here.
I'm eight and three quarters. Mr. How old are you?
Mr. You're boring.
Listen, kid, I'd like some peace and quiet, please.
You're grumpy. Mr. Is that why that woman left you on the
bench? Was she your girlfriend?
No, she wasn't.
Listen, I have a girlfriend. Mr. And I'm
only in the second grade. Where's your girlfriend?
My wife Elizabeth is
gone.
Well, where has she gone to?
She's gone. Gone dead.
Oh, that's sad.
Well, my girlfriend Katie, she's still really young.
Was she a good girlfriend?
Katie's the best I've had,
yes. Elizabeth was one of a kind.
Why? Have you ever had any other girlfriends?
Yesterday I brought Katie a flower and she
gave me a kiss on the cheek.
Have you ever brought a girl a flower? Kid, you've got a
lot to learn about relationships. Have you ever looked
into someone's eyes and had a whole conversation in an
instant,
laughed with someone, kept laughing until you even forgot
why you were laughing?
Have you ever cried? I cried last night when I said goodbye
to Katie,
but that was because I had scraped my knee badly.
Mr. Yes.
Are you going to get a new girlfriend for all those things?
No. I'm happy just by myself.
I think you're grumpy.
I have lots of girlfriends. Mr. Over six.
Lizie was my one and only.
You talk about your girlfriend a lot. My wife.
I love getting girlfriends. Mr. You should try it.
There's not enough time left for me for those kind of shenanigans.
Plus, I thought I was a boring,
grumpy old guy. Nah,
you're nice. Well, once you stop breeding.
See that pretty girl over there?
I'm about to get a new girlfriend in 10 seconds.
There's always time.
Got to go. Mr. Bye bye.
Nice day, isn't it? Yeah,
it's beautiful. Really? Enjoy the park.
Me? Hi. I'm trying to
relax. Would you mind?
Oh, sorry. Mr.
Hey, kid,
just come over here and sit down, would you?
What's your name? Mr. My name is Adam.
You look like my grandpa, except he's not as old.
That's very rude. I'm Adam.
Who are you?
Joseph. Where's your mother?
She's with her boyfriend. Supposed to wait over
here. I'm eight
and three quarters. Mr. How old are you?
Mr. You're boring.
Listen, kid, I'd like some peace and quiet, please.
You're grumpy. Mr. Is that why that woman left you on the
bench? Was she your girlfriend?
No, she wasn't.
Listen, I have a girlfriend. Mr. And I'm only in
the second grade. Where's your girlfriend?
My wife Elizabeth is
gone.
Well, where has she gone to? She's gone.
Gone dead.
Oh, that's sad.
Well, my girlfriend Katie, she's still really young.
Was she a good girlfriend?
Katie's the best I've had,
yes. Elizabeth was one of a kind.
Why? Have you ever had any other girlfriends?
Yesterday I brought Katie a flower and she gave me
a kiss on the cheek.
Have you ever brought a girl a flower? Kid, you've got a
lot to learn about relationships. Have you ever looked
into someone's eyes and had a whole conversation in
an instant,
laughed with someone, kept laughing until you even forgot
why you were laughing? Have you
ever cried? I cried last night when I said goodbye to Katie,
but that was because I had scraped my knee badly.
Mr. Yes.
Are you going to get a new girlfriend for all those things?
No. I'm happy just by myself.
I think you're grumpy.
I have lots of girlfriends. Mr. Over six.
Lizie was my one and only.
You talk about your girlfriend a lot. My wife.
I love getting girlfriends. Mr. You should try it.
There's not enough time left for me for those kind of shenanigans.
Plus, I thought I was a boring, grumpy old
guy. Nah,
you're nice. Well, once you stop breeding.
See that pretty girl over there?
I'm about to get a new girlfriend in 10 seconds.
There's always time.
Got to go. Mr. Bye bye.
Nice day, isn't it? Yeah,
it's beautiful. Really? Enjoy the park.